# YAUHENIYA ZIALENKA

JR. FRONT-END DEVELOPER



# **EDUCATION**

Family physician

Belarusian State Medical University

2013 - 2019

Front-end/JS Course

The Rolling Scopes School

June, 2022 - September, 2023

**EXPERIENCE** 

Nurse, 2017-2018

Hospital, MInsk

Nurse

Oncology Center, Minsk

**Doctor** 

Hospital, Minsk

Junior Front-end developer

freelance

### FrontEnd intern

Eventizer StartUp

September, 2022 - now

# **EXPERTISE**

Html5, CSS3,

Scss,

Fetch

TypeScript

JavaScript

**ESLint** 

HTTP,HTTPS

Yarn, npm

Webpack

Github

Grid

git,

React, React Hooks

react-router-dom, react-hook-form

**REST API** 

Next.js

2017-2018

2018-2019

2019-2022

2022-now

#### FlexBox Windows,

MacOS

Figma

OOP

Responsive Web design

Jest, Vitest

SPA

firebase

Vite

# **PROFILE**

## My name is Yauhenia.

I'm 27 years old. I devoted 9 years to medicine and decided to change the field of activity. Now I study Front-end at Rolling Scopes School courses and I have 1 years of development experience.

I easily assimilate information, learn quickly, can easily switch from one task to another, like to cope with non-standard situations. I'm stress resistant, calm and ready to action.

I'm looking for a job or internship in Front-end development. I'm interesting in reactive technologies, especially React. My forte is medicine, so I can be very usefull in projects connected with wellness and health. But also curious and open to different spheres.

# LANGUAGES

Russian, English - B2, Polish(beginner)

# **PROJECTS**

Rolling Scopes test projects Eventizer

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/ evgueniazet-JSFE2022Q3/online-zoo/

https://evgueniazet.github.io/cssBayan/ cssBayan/index.html

https://commandor05-online-store.netlify.app/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/ evgueniazet-JSFE2022Q3/songbird/

https://rolling-scopes-school.github.io/ evgueniazet-JSFE2023Q1/rs-css/

# **CONTACTS**

email: zelenkoea19@gmail.com

**phone:** +375 25 538 43 25, +48 511 250 189 github: <a href="https://github.com/evgueniazet">https://github.com/evgueniazet</a>